<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>regulation on Smart Contract Stack - Weekly Crypto, NFT, Blockchain Digest</title>
    <link>https://smartcontractstack.com/tags/regulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in regulation on Smart Contract Stack - Weekly Crypto, NFT, Blockchain Digest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://smartcontractstack.com/tags/regulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 16 - 2023</title>
      <link>https://smartcontractstack.com/posts/w16-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smartcontractstack.com/posts/w16-2023/</guid>
      <description>blockchain connecting the world within world within world news U.S. crypto exchange Coinbase secures Bermuda licence | Reuters (reuters.com) | [💬 discussion] - Major U.S. crypto exchange Coinbase Global Inc has said it has secured a licence to operate in Bermuda, as part of a wider push to expand globally.
Transactions on Arbitrum Surpass Bitcoin — Along With Fees - Blockworks (blockworks.co) - Even as transactions accelerate, the cost to use the Arbitrum blockchain remains low</description>
      <content>
  &lt;figure class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://smartcontractstack.com/img/w16-2023-smartcontractstack.png&#34;  alt=&#34;blockchain connecting the world within world within world&#34;   style=&#34;border-radius: 7px;&#34;  /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34;  style=&#34;color: white;&#34; &gt;blockchain connecting the world within world within world&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;h1 id=&#34;news&#34;&gt;news&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-crypto-exchange-coinbase-secures-bermuda-licence-2023-04-20/&#34;&gt;U.S. crypto exchange Coinbase secures Bermuda licence | Reuters&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(reuters.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 | [&lt;a href=&#34;https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=35661977&#34;&gt;💬 discussion&lt;/a&gt;] - Major U.S. crypto exchange Coinbase Global Inc has said it has secured a licence to operate in Bermuda, as part of a wider push to expand globally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blockworks.co/news/transactions-arbitrum-bitcoin-fees&#34;&gt;Transactions on Arbitrum Surpass Bitcoin — Along With Fees - Blockworks&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(blockworks.co)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Even as transactions accelerate, the cost to use the Arbitrum blockchain remains low&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blockworks.co/news/transunion-crypto-defi-credit-scores&#34;&gt;Borrowing Crypto With DeFi? TransUnion Shares Real-world Credit Scores - Blockworks&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(blockworks.co)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - TransUnion is paying close attention to the crypto ecosystem, now connecting DeFi protocols with real-world credit scores&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blockworks.co/news/texas-proof-of-reserves-bill-advances-to-senate&#34;&gt;Texas ‘Proof of Reserves’ Bill Advances to Senate - Blockworks&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(blockworks.co)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - The bill focuses on digital asset providers who have $10 million in customer funds or over 500 customers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://decrypt.co/137503/crypto-vc-funding-down-82-percent&#34;&gt;Crypto VC Funding Down 82% Compared to Last Year - Decrypt&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(decrypt.co)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - The evaporating funding means &amp;ldquo;a lot of companies are doing their down rounds,&amp;rdquo; said the founder of Delta Blockchain Fund.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://decrypt.co/137144/hong-kong-is-vying-to-be-the-next-crypto-hub&#34;&gt;Hong Kong Is Vying To Be The Next Crypto Hub - Decrypt&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(decrypt.co)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Hong Kong has historically provided fertile soil to grow financial institutions. Can it also make magic for crypto firms?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/cowswap/status/1647962756400701443&#34;&gt;🐦 view tweet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(twitter.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Say hello to &lt;em&gt;partially fillable limit orders&lt;/em&gt; from CoW Swap. Now enabled by default, partial fills bring faster trade settlement to limit orders – even in moments of low liquidity. 🏃💨&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dlnews.com/articles/defi/sherlock-defi-insurer-on-edge-euler-hack/&#34;&gt;DeFi insurer Sherlock teeters on the edge after reserves fall 90% – DL News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(dlnews.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Sherlock, a platform that insures the integrity of computer code powering DeFi protocols, is in dire straits. Over the last year, its reserves have fallen by 90%, to $3 million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cointelegraph.com/news/subgraph-hosted-service-launches-as-the-graph-prepares-for-decentralization&#34;&gt;Subgraph hosted service launches as The Graph prepares for decentralization&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(cointelegraph.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - The new service will make it easier for mid-tier or small-tier subgraphs to be indexed and discovered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/blockblanc/status/1648998168527360001&#34;&gt;🐦 view tweet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(twitter.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - 🕊️ @Free__Alexey IS FREE TO GO HOME  🕊️&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/EnsoFinance/status/1649049560696909824&#34;&gt;🐦 view tweet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(twitter.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Use Enso now to navigate all of DeFi from a single dashboard with a single click!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1649056938062118913&#34;&gt;🐦 view tweet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(twitter.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - France launched a stablecoin on Ethereum and it&amp;rsquo;s the worst code I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/20/eu-parliament-approves-crypto-licensing-funds-transfer-rules/&#34;&gt;The European Parliament Has Voted for the EU&amp;rsquo;s Landmark MiCA Regulation and Anti-Money Laundering Transfer of Funds Rules&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(coindesk.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Lawmakers in the European Union on Thursday voted 517-38 in favor of a new crypto licensing regime, Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA), with 18 absentions, making it the first major jurisdiction in the world to introduce a comprehensive crypto law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;tool&#34;&gt;tool&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.joinfire.xyz/&#34;&gt;Fire - Web3 Safety Tool&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(joinfire.xyz)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Fire is a free browser extension that simulates web3 transactions, showing you exactly what will enter and exit your wallet before you sign the contract. All under control with your current wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vcdata.site/&#34;&gt;Venture Funding Events In Web3  ·  Web3 VC Data&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(vcdata.site)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - The data is a mix of enterprise sources which have been licensed and founders sharing their data. The numbers go back to 2021. This is still a beta product. Originally inspired by Dove Metrics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://viem.sh/&#34;&gt;viem · TypeScript Interface for Ethereum&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(viem.sh)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Build reliable apps &amp;amp; libraries with lightweight, composable, and type-safe modules that interface with Ethereum&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/OffcierCia/On-Chain-Investigations-Tools-List&#34;&gt;GitHub - OffcierCia/On-Chain-Investigations-Tools-List: Here we discuss how one can investigate crypto hacks and security incidents, and collect all the possible tools and manuals! PRs are welcome! If any tool is missing - please open PR!&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(github.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Here we discuss how one can investigate crypto hacks and security incidents, and collect all the possible tools and manuals! PRs are welcome! If any tool is missing - please open PR!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;misc&#34;&gt;misc&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.coindesk.com/podcasts/the-breakdown-with-nlw/sergey-nazarov-on-why-the-world-needs-a-new-model-of-cryptographic-trust/&#34;&gt;Sergey Nazarov on Why the World Needs a New Model of (Cryptographic) Trust&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(coindesk.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - NLW is joined by Chainlink co-founder Sergey Nazarov for the first in “The Breakdown”&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Paradigm Shift&amp;rdquo; interview series. Sergey discusses why society&amp;rsquo;s trust model has broken down, how cryptographic truth serves as an alternative, and why this alternative method of understanding truth will become even more important as a countermeasure to artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://starkware.medium.com/what-are-storage-proofs-and-how-can-they-improve-oracles-e0379108720a&#34;&gt;What are Storage Proofs and how can they improve Oracles? | by StarkWare | Apr, 2023 | Medium&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(starkware.medium.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Storage proofs are a cryptographic way to track blockchain information so that it can be shared across chains. Similar to oracles, storage proofs provide proof that the information is true. However…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://token.unlocks.app/ethereum-shanghai&#34;&gt;The Best Ethereum Shanghai Upgrade Massive Unlock Dashboard&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(token.unlocks.app)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Ethereum Shanghai Unlocks Dashboard from TokenUnlocks provides real-time updates on staked ETH withdrawals and validator insights for the hard fork.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/johnrising_/status/1647859209126412289&#34;&gt;🐦 view tweet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(twitter.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - One downside of Smart Accounts is that transaction fees are higher. But how much more expensive are they really? I crunched the numbers and posted them to Stackup&amp;rsquo;s blog 🤓&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/doganeth_en/status/1640062610161688577&#34;&gt;🐦 view tweet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(twitter.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - Introducing Opclave: An Op Stack chain that enables to turn iPhone&amp;rsquo;s into a hardware wallet with fully Account Abstraction support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/apes_prologue/status/1648654431322349568&#34;&gt;🐦 view tweet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;sub&gt;(twitter.com)&lt;/sub&gt;
 - $PEPE: Mysterious Whales&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
